# PORTIA J SYDNEY ASSOCIATE/ANALYST

5/132 D1, Kalyan Nagar, Aligarh, UP ↑
+91- 7409129413

portiajsydney27@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/portia-j-sydney-180893179 ✓ in

Experienced in identifying and coordinating process improvement initiatives that incorporate best practices and standard operating procedures. Skillfully identifies, plans and implements prioritized projects for organizational transformation. Advanced proficiency and demonstrated skill managing and driving multiple projects with minimal supervision.

## **Experience**

## Operational Associate / Eventenoo Events, Aligarh

(OCT 2020 - JAN 2022)

- Submitted quote requests to suppliers to determine best rates for organization.
- Streamlined office operations by computerizing activities, managing customer communications, scheduling payments and tracking records and documents.
- Created plan to streamline onboarding and operational support for clients.

## Process Advisor / Barclays, Noida

(DEC 2019 - SEP 2020)

- Identified and resolved process issues to drive optimal workflow and business growth.
- Partnered with cross-functional teams to conduct thorough discovery and due diligence on existing processes.
- Customer Services, Payment protection Insurance, understanding the detail Retail Banking Products, verification of data, checking customer's account, payment to a customer, taking care of fund transfer to customer account, creating consolidated payment MI Reports.

## Process Associate / Capgemini, Noida

(MAY 2019 - OCT 2019)

- US Healthcare Medical Billing Claim Process (Health Insurance portability and accountability act).
- Validation of authorization and duplicate in every claim. Processed high dollar claims (claim releasing authorization for Medical-\$10,000).

## **Achievements**

• Workshop on "Android App Dev & Web Designing" with Google SEO.

### **Skills**

- Problem Solving
- Customer Service
- Communication
- Data Entry
- HR
- Business Process

#### **Education**

MBA / Arunachal University of Studies

2019 - 2021 | CGPA: 6.64

BCA / Himalayan University

2014 - 2017 | CGPA: 7.38

HSC/Intermediate / Ingraham Institute Aligarh

2013 – 2014 | CGPA: 6.32